５秒でいい ミスターブラウンの
注意を引きつけ
実験による衝撃が起きたことを
気付かないようにしてもらいたい
分かった 分かった
そうなったら
色仕掛けだね
Just for five seconds,
触ってみ 結構 硬いから
I want you to draw Mr. Braun's attention,
あっ 確かに
でしょ？ 任せて！
so he doesn't notice any
shaking from the experiment.
色仕掛けだよな？
Got it!
そうだけど？
まあ いい 頼むぞ
I'll just have to seduce him.
オーキードーキー
Want to touch it?
It's pretty firm.
ふっ！
It is.
Right?
うっ… ううっ…
Leave it to me.
You're seducing him, right?
Yup, what about it?
はっ！
Never mind. I'm counting on you.
Okey-dokey.
今だ！
助手よ 決行だ！
何だ？
あっ？ 岡… あっ…
あっちゃ～ 失敗…
てめえ 何度 言ったら… うおっ！
Now!
Assistant, go!
What?
うう…
止まった？
Oh, no... I failed.
助手が？ いや…
How many times do I have to tell you?
あっ…
It stopped?
うん？ あ…
My assistant?
No...
これは… まさか…
ああ…
何が…
うん？
｢まさか｣だ！
だっ…！
What is this?
No way!
What do you mean...
"No way"?
Dogma in Event Horizon
つまり 偶然にも
１階の 42型ブラウン管が
In other words,
the 42" CRT on the first floor
just happens to function as the lifter.
リフターの代わりとして
作用していた
故に 工房が営業中で
テレビがついている時間しか
So we were only able to send
D-mail when the studio was open
and the TV was on...
Ｄメールを送れなかった か…
確かに 説明がつくわね
That makes a lot of sense!
大声を出すな 頭に響く…
大丈夫？
Don't be so loud. It hurts my head...
Are you okay?
ミスターブラウンめ…
Mr. Braun...
暴力に訴えるとは…
I never thought you would resort to violence.
まあ 自業自得ともいえるけどね
In a way, it's your own fault.
実験をしたいと言ったのは
貴様だろう
You're the one who wanted to run an experiment!
痛て…
とにかく
Anyway, we almost completely understand
これで 電話レンジの仕組みは
ほぼ 解明できた
how the Phone Microwave works now.
となると 次は…
Which means that next...
物理的タイムトラベルの
可能性について 考えるべきだろう
We should consider physically transporting
an object through time.
無理
１秒で否定するな！
Impossible.
Don't dismiss it so quickly!
どう 工夫しても
ゲル状になるのがオチよ
It's going to end up jelly, no matter what we do.
大体 人間を
36バイトなんてデータに… あっ
And how the heck do you
fit a human into 36 bytes...
うん？
こんなときに自慢か？
Is this really the time for showing off?
あんたに自慢して どうするのよ
論文のタイトルを見て
Why would I want to show off to you?
Look at the title of my paper.
うん？
"The Analysis of Nerve Pulse Signals
｢側頭葉に蓄積された
記憶に関する
Stored in Memory Within the Temporal Lobe."
神経パルス信号の解析｣
日本語でＯＫだよ
Can I get that in Japanese?
要するに 人の記憶に関する論文
Essentially, it has to do with people's memories.
I majored in neuroscience.
脳科学専攻なの 私
はあ…？
Put simply,
脳の中の記憶は 簡単に言うと
the brain stores memories as pulse signals.
パルス信号によって
蓄積されていくものなの
一種の電気的なデータ
They're a type of electrical data.
データ… まさか！
Data... You can't mean...
そう 人間を物理的に送ることは
到底 無理だけど
That's right.
Sending a human through time is impossible,
記憶データだけなら
送ることは可能かもしれない
but it might be possible to send their memory data.
どこに？
過去の自分によ
Me on 2010/8/13 AD                    Hippocampus
Where?
To the you in the past.
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals  -->  Encode to Electric Signals
記憶をデータ化して
Ｄメールと同じ要領で過去に送る
We turn the memories into data,
and we send them back,
the same way as with the D-mail.
要は 今の自分の頭の中身だけを
過去の自分に移植するわけ
Basically, you're transplanting your
present brain's contents into the past.
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
つまり 過去に自分が戻る！
In other words, "you" go back to the past!
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!                     Receive
タイムトラベルというよりは
タイムリープね
It's more of a time leap than time travel.
俺だ
うん？
It's me.
All the lines have converged at one point.
すべての線は 一本に つながった
計画は これより最終段階に入る
The plan will now enter its final stages.
現代を司る女神…
｢現在を司る女神作戦｣の開始だ！
The goddess who rules the present...
Begin Operation Verdandi!
わけ わかめ
ほえ～
Begin what now?
Explain what you're talking about a little.
少しは
どういうことか説明しなさいよ！
なっ… お前の言うタイムリープを
採用すると言っているのだ
I'm saying we're going to do that
time leap you're talking about.
Begin now.
すぐに始めろ
…って言われても
But we'll need a lot of stuff to do it.
開発には いくつか材料が必要よ
もっとも 側頭葉に蓄積されている
記憶の信号
Of course, we only have to read
memories stored in the temporal lobe,
読み取ればいいだけだから
秋葉で そろうと思うけど…
so I think I can get everything in Akiba...
ただ…
うん？ どうした？
But...
What's wrong?
一つは 電話レンジじゃ
人間の記憶のﾃﾞｰﾀを圧縮するには
One problem is that
I don't think the Phone Microwave will be able
力不足の可能性が高いってこと
to sufficiently compress the memory data.
それと…
何だ？
And...
What?
あっ… いえ…
Nothing.
いいわ
今 必要なパーツを書き出すから
All right.
I'll make a list of parts I need for now.
まゆしぃは
難しすぎて さっぱりです
It's too hard for Mayushii to understand it at all.
さっき クリスティーナも
言っていたではないか
Christina just explained it.
今の… この自分の意識を
過去に飛ばすのだ
You're sending your mind,
as it exists right now, to the past.
う～ん… なんか おっかなそう…
Sounds scary.
Ｄメールじゃ ダメなのかな？
Is the D-mail not good enough?
There are too many
chaotic variables with the D-mail.
Ｄメールは不確定要素が多すぎる
たった 一通のメールで
予期せぬことが起きてしまう
One message can change
things you'd never expect.
記憶を過去に戻すのは平気なの？
But it's okay to send memories into the past?
If nothing else, you can
少なくとも 過去改変について
ある程度
コントロールが可能になる
prevent the past from changing, to a degree.
秋葉の町を変えてしまうような
変化は…
You wouldn't have the
entire city of Akiba changing...
町を？
The city?
ああ いや… 何でもない
Nothing, never mind.
あれ？ でも…
Huh?
But what happens to you
記憶を過去に送った後の自分は
どうなっちゃうんだろう？
after you send your memories?
Your body is still here, isn't it?
体は
ここに残ったままなんでしょ？
うん それは…
Well...
それと 今 まゆしぃは こうやって
オカリンと お話してるでしょ？
So, Mayushii is talking to Okarin now, right?
ああ
その まゆしぃが
Then, you're saying Mayushii goes back a week,
１週間前に飛んで １週間を
やり直したとするでしょ？
and then relives the week, right?
その時 オカリンと
お話しないように行動したら
What happens if she doesn't talk to Okarin this time?
どうなっちゃうのかな？
それは…
I assume that you would recall that we spoke,
恐らく まゆりの中に記憶は残るが
話したという事実は消える
but the fact of our having spoken would be erased.
つまり まゆしぃは
お話したことを覚えてるのに
In other words, Mayushii would remember us talking,
オカリンは
全然 知らないってことになるの？
but Okarin wouldn't?
そうだな
I'd imagine so.
Then, that's kind of sad.
だとしたらね
なんだか さみしいね
うん？ 俺が？
For me?
ううん
Nope.
まゆしぃが
For Mayushii.
あっ 萌郁さんだ
んっ…
It's Moeka-san!
Moeka-san!
萌郁さ～ん！
あっ…
トゥットゥルー！
随分 浮かない顔をしているな
閃光の指圧師よ
You look rather unhappy, Shining Finger.
あっ？
｢タイムマシンは破棄した？｣
"Did you get rid of the time machine?"
We're still using it.
まだ 使ってるよ それでね
And now, we might be able to do a time leap—
今度は タイムリープが
できるかもしれないんだって
Don't tell her about that!
軽々しく話すな！
え～！
But Moeka-san's a lab member, too, right?
でも 萌郁さんも ラボメンだよ
ああ それはそうだが… うん？
She is, but...
｢タイムリープって何？｣
"What's a time leap?"
ううっ… 文字どおりの意味だ
Just what it sounds like!
記憶の時間跳躍を可能にする…
We can send memories through time.
記憶の？
Memories...
萌郁さん？
Moeka-san?
おっ おお…
えっ？
ああ… 萌郁さ～ん…
Moeka-san!
大丈夫かなぁ？
Is she okay?
うん？
｢あきばお～｣を先に回った方が
効率的か
It would be faster to head for Akibaoo first, I guess?
まゆりおねえちゃん！
うん？
Mayuri-oneechan!
おおっ 今度は 綯ちゃんだ～
It's Nae-chan!
どうしたの？
What's wrong?
Yo.
うい～っす
うん？
You're still dressed like that?
まだ その格好なのか…
いや～
店長に 一日 それでいろって
怒られちゃってさ
The boss told me to stay this way all day.
良い子には 微妙に目の毒だぞ
You'll poison children's minds.
毒？ 毒物は
持ち歩かないようにしてるけど…
Poison?
I'm careful never to walk around with poison.
はあ？
ああ それより 綯がさ
Huh?
Anyway, Nae said she wanted to
岡部 倫太郎に話があるって
捜してたんだよ
talk to Okabe Rintarou, so we were looking for you.
俺に？
うん
To me?
I'm sorry!
ごめんなさい さっきは
お父さんが ひどいことして…
My dad was really mean back there!
綯ちゃん…
Nae-chan...
You came all this way to say that?
それを言うために わざわざ…
なんと よく出来た小動物
What a well-trained little pet.
She's not a pet.
小動物じゃないよ
Don't worry.
案ずるな
俺も ミスターブラウンには
I cause trouble for Mr. Braun all the time.
いつも 迷惑をかけている
おあいこだ
We're even.
That's not like the Okabe Rintarou I know...
岡部 倫太郎っぽくないね～
ええ～？
オカリンは いつも こうだよ
Okarin's always like this.
ふ～ん…
Mayushii's gonna get going, okay?
じゃあ まゆしぃは
そろそろ 行くのです
待ち合わせか？
うん レイヤーのフブキちゃん
Meeting someone?
Yup!
I'm going to give the cosplayer, Fubuki-chan, her outfit.
コス 渡しに行くんだ
Come to think of it, it's almost time for Comima.
そういや そろそろ コミマか…
Yup.
うん じゃあね～
鈴さんと 綯ちゃんも
Bye!
See you, Suzu-san and Nae-chan!
トゥットゥルー！
See you!
またね～ フフフ…
Okay, let's head back ourselves.
じゃ あたしらも帰ろうか
No, I need to find the parts Christina asked me for.
いや 俺は まだ クリスティーナに
頼まれた パーツを探さねば…
あっ…
牧瀬 紅莉栖は
ＳＥＲＮに通じている
Makise Kurisu works with SERN.
あっ… えっ？
ＳＥＲＮのスパイ… まさかな
A SERN spy?
No way.
ぬるぽ
ガッ
All your base are...
...belong to us.
あっ！ あっ…
音もなく近づくなんて 反則よ！
You can't sneak up on me!
It's against the rules!
フフ…
やはり 書き込んでいたのは
So, you were posting on @channel.
＠ちゃんねるか
ちょっ これは 別に…
I realized you were an @channeler a long time ago.
貴様が 生粋の＠ちゃんねらーだと
気付いたのは 随分 前だ
I wasn't, no...
今更 隠したところで
何の意味もない
No!
There's no point in hiding it now.
うう… 鬱だ…
This sucks...
All right.
まあ いい これから ｸﾘｽﾃｨｰﾅには
ねらーの称号を正式に与える
From now on,
I officially give you the title of Channeler...
これ以上
変な呼び名を付け足すな！
Don't give me any more weird nicknames!
And please, keep this a secret!
っていうか
ないしょにしておいてよ！
Why?
なぜだ？ 履歴書に
堂々と書けばいいではないか
You could list it on your resume.
If they knew a serious academic were posting,
｢趣味 ＠ちゃんねる｣と
学者が ねらーとなれば
スレの一つや二つ 立つだろう
they'd probably make a few threads about you.
Why would I care?
立って どうする…
なら
Then what? You'd sage them?
ＶＩＰで安価を出すことの方が
いいと言うのか？
くうっ… 意味が分かる自分が憎い
I hate myself for understanding that last sentence.
しかし 安心したぞ
Either way, I feel better.
I can't imagine
そこまで
自分を隠すのが下手な人間が
anyone who's so terrible at hiding things
スパイとは考えられんな
being a spy.
はあ？ 何 それ
What does that mean?
いや バイト戦士が
The part-time warrior said you were a SERN spy.
クリスティーナは
ＳＥＲＮのスパイだと 言いだして
What is that supposed to mean?
なんなのよ その言いがかり
そんなわけないでしょ…
まったくだ
That's impossible.
Indeed.
貴様は 機関から送られてきた
エージェントであり
You're an agent the Organization sent,
今は 心を入れ替え
我が助手として
who's had a change of heart
and now works as my assistant.
働いているのだからな
それも違う
That's not true, either.
それで 作業の方は
どうなっているのだ？
So how's the work going?
作業？
タイムリープだ
Work?
The time leap.
I bought all the parts.
パーツは すべて買ってきたぞ
Oh... That's right.
ああ… そうよね 作るべきよね
I should make it, shouldn't I?
ここまで来たんだから…
I've come this far.
うん？ どういうことだ？
What is this?
You're getting scared?
怖くなったのか？
それもある
That, too...
I keep asking myself what will happen
if we really make it.
もし 本当に出来てしまったら
どうなるんだろうって…
けど それより…
何だ？
But more than that...
What?
I should tell you...
話しておくべきね
It seems like it's half-obvious already.
どうせ こっちも
半分は バレてるみたいだし
やっぱり ここじゃ無理
I can't do it here!
あんたの顔が見えないとこにして
うん？
Let's go somewhere I can't see your face.
私 父親との間に
ちょっと 問題を抱えてるの
I've got a problem with my dad...
では アーカンソーで雷に打たれ
クリスティーナの父が
So your father was struck by lightning,
on the grassy plains of Arkansas,
and fell to the dark side—
ダークサイドに落ちたという…
ちゃかすなら もう話さない
If you're going to be a jerk, I'm not telling you.
分かった 聞かせてもらおう
All right. Tell me.
簡単に言うと 父に嫌われているの
To put it simply, my dad doesn't like me.
No... He hates me.
ううん 憎まれてる
And not as his daughter. As a scientist, as a rival.
しかも 娘じゃなく
科学者として ライバルとして
My dad was a physicist.
私の父は物理学者だったの
I always liked hearing him
私は 小さい頃から
父の難しい物理学の話を
聞くのが好きだった
talk about the details of his work.
おかげで 小学校の高学年ぐらいで
And so, by the end of elementary school,
I could understand his papers.
父の論文が
理解できるようになったわ
そして 自分で論文を書いたり
賞をもらえるようになった
And then, I started writing my own papers,
and winning awards.
でも 賞なんて どうでもよかった
But I didn't care about the awards.
I loved debating with my father.
私は 父と議論ができるのが
楽しかった
We exchanged papers by e-mail,
メールで いくつも論文を交わして
議論を深めて
and our debates got deeper.
But...
でも…
Eventually, my dad stopped debating with me.
いつしか
父は 私の相手をしなくなった
議論を楽しんでいる間に
私は 論破していたの
While I enjoyed the debates,
I was also winning them.
父の誤りを指摘し
I pointed out mistakes he'd made,
and without even thinking about it, I hurt his pride.
父のプライドを
知らずに傷つけていた
My dad started taking it out on my mom.
父は 母に当たるようになった
He lost confidence,
自信を失って
次第に 学会から見放されていった
and began withdrawing from his academic peers.
最後に会った時に
父は 私に こう言ったの
The last time I saw him,
he said this to me...
"Do you pity me?
｢私を哀れんでいるのか？
さげすんでいるのか？
Do you look down on me?"
"You're my daughter. How dare you."
娘の分際で｣って…
If I make a device that enables a time leap,
タイムリープできる装置を
私が作ったとしたら
I think my dad might go insane.
父は 間違いなく 怒り狂うと思う
今まで以上に
Even more than before...
So that's why you're hesitant to make it?
それで
作るのを ためらっていたのか？
でも 心配しないで
どうせ 作るから
But don't worry.
I'll end up doing it, regardless.
あんたが言うように
私は 実験 大好きだから
Just like you said, I love experimenting.
何かを見つけたら
確かめずには いられない
If I see a possibility, I have to investigate it.
父が そうだったように
Just like my dad used to...
The time I spent with my dad...
父と私が過ごした時間が
そうだったように
...was like that.
Then we begin Operation Verdandi immediately!
ならば すぐに！
うん？
｢現在を司る女神作戦｣に
取りかかる！
モタモタしてる暇はない！
There's no time to waste!
The Organization stands at our very doorstep!
機関は すぐ そこに
迫っているのだから！
That's your response?
結局 それ？
当たり前だ！
Of course...
I am Hououin Kyouma.
俺は 鳳凰院 凶真
I have a destiny to change the world!
世界の構造を変革する
使命がある！
はぁ… 話すんじゃなかった
I shouldn't have said anything...
それと同時に和解にも行く
And we'll reconcile you with your dad, too!
父親は 今 どこにいる？
Where is he?
えっ？ あ 青森だけど…
H-He's in Aomori.
We'll need money to go...
行くとなれば 資金の問題もある
時期が決まったら
早めに声をかけてくれ
When you work out the time,
tell me as soon as you can.
って…
まさか 一緒に来るつもりか？
You can't mean to go with me.
Naturally!
当たり前だ
お前には 我が野望のため
I need you in peak mental condition,
so you can further my ambitions!
最高の精神状態で
働いてもらわねばならん
この 鳳凰院 凶真が
一緒に行って
I, Hououin Kyouma, shall accompany you.
And I shall use my masterful people skills
その場の空気を読んだ
見事な話題を提供し
親子の わだかまりを
解消してやる
to reunite father and daughter.
What?
なにそれ…
You're a self-proclaimed mad scientist, right?
あんた 自称 ﾏｯﾄﾞｻｲｴﾝﾃｨｽﾄでしょ？
Since when do mad scientists have people skills?
空気 読んで どうするのよ
Well, um, you see...
なっ… そ それはだな…
フフッ… フフ…
なぜ 笑う？
Why are you laughing?
Sometimes you're a good guy, you know?
あんたって たまに
いいヤツだから 困るのよね
That's the problem.
俺の偉大さが分かったら
作業に戻れ
Now that you understand
my greatness, back to work.
Right, right!
はいはい
言っとくけど もう 決定だから
Just so we're clear, this is now decided.
無理やりでも 連れていくからな
So I'm dragging you with me,
whether you want to go or not!
Sounds good to me.
望むところだ
トゥッ… トゥル～…
うう～…
Mayuri-chan?
あれ まゆりちゃん？
はぁ…
What's with all this stuff?
どうしたの？ こんな大荷物
Shouldn't you call that Okarin guy?
オカリンとかいうのを
呼んだ方がいいんじゃないの？
It's okay...
大丈夫 もう少しなので…
I'm almost there.
Look at the label!
ここ見なさいよ！
ちゃんと書いてあるでしょ
It says "Makise" right here!
｢牧瀬｣って！
｢牧瀬プリン｣と読めるではないか
It reads "Makise pudding."
森永さんちのプリンも
小岩井さんちのプリンも
That's just a brand name,
like Morinaga pudding or Koiwai pudding.
同じだろ
へりくつを言うな！
Don't play stupid!
大体 ｢牧瀬｣とは何者だ？
私の名前だ！
Who's "Makise," anyway?
That's my name!
｢クリスティーナ牧瀬｣か
"Christina Makise"?
If only you'd written "Christina" instead,
だったら 素直に
｢クリスティーナ｣と書いておけば
I wouldn't have accidentally
ingested the extra calories.
うっかり 無駄なカロリーを
摂取せずに済んだものを
Don't eat other people's food!
ひとのものを勝手に食べといて…
And that's my spoon! Don't use it!
大体 それ 私のスプーンでしょ
勝手に使わないでよ！
You use the lab's forks, don't you?!
貴様も ラボのフォークを
勝手に使っているではないか！
ふぅ 到着…
I'm here...
ふい～！
うん？ あっ どうしたの？ それ
What's all that?
Mayushii's cosplay materials and sleepover set!
コスの材料と
まゆしぃの お泊まりセットだよ～
お泊まり？
うん
Sleepover?
Yup!
I'm going to make some
cosplay outfits for Comima.
コミマ用のコスを作るのです
Are you sure?
本当に 大丈夫なの？ ご両親は？
What about your parents?
I told them about it.
ちゃんと 言ってきたよ
You're staying over, too, right?
紅莉栖ちゃんも お泊まりでしょ？
電話レンジの改良で
To work on the Phone Microwave?
えっ？ そうね
そうしようかと思っていたけど…
Yeah, I thought I might.
But it's kind of depressing to be here.
ただ ここに泊まると
気が めいるのよね
There's this Hououin something guy
鳳凰院 何とかさんが
勝手に ひとのプリンを食べるから
who goes around eating people's pudding.
あっ… 鳳凰院 凶真だ！
名前ぐらい覚えろ！
It's Hououin Kyouma!
Learn my name, already!
You're the last person I want to hear that from!
あんたに言われたくない！
つうか プリンの方はスルーか！
And don't ignore the part about the pudding!
Maybe I should leave?
帰った方がいいかなぁ？
No, I'll stay,
へっ？ あっ…
ああ 私は 泊まってもいいけど
but if I do, then Okabe should leave.
だとしたら
岡部は出てった方がいいわね
なんだとぅ!?
What?!
The lab is the house of my soul!
俺にとって ラボは魂の住みか！
出ていくなど…
I could never leave—
なぜ 一緒に泊まる条件が
買い出しに行くことになるのだ？
Why is her condition for staying that I go shopping?
Come to think of it,
考えてみれば 昨日から ずっと
I've been running errands
for my assistant since yesterday.
助手のお使いをしているような…
うん？ クリスティーナか…
Christina?
From: Assistant
Subject: I demand compensation and an apology
I demand two puddings,
as punishment for the one you ate. And...
We're taking a late bus to Aomori,
due to finances.
フン… ｢何を浮かれている？
ラボメンとしての本分を忘れるな｣
"What are you so happy about?
Don't forget your role as a lab member."
浮かれてなんかないわよ バカ！
I'm not happy, stupid!
ほえ？ 何？
What?
It's nothing!
あっ… ああ 何でもないわ
Let's get in, before Okabe gets back.
早く 入っちゃうわよ
岡部が戻ってくる前に
Okay.
うん
うん？ また助手か？
My assistant again?
ちっ…
You know too much.
What?
何だ？
ううっ… ああ…
あっ！
あっ… まゆり…
Mayuri...
おおっと…
Mayuri!
まゆり… まゆり！
はあっ… はあっ…
はっ… はっ… はっ…
はっ… はっ… ぐっ…
はあっ… はあっ…
はぁ… はぁ…
うん？
あっ あっ… ああ…
ゆっ… ゆっ…
I'll never forgive you! Ever!
許さない！
絶対 許さないからな！
Okarin, Mayushii is very sad
and very embarrassed.
オカリン
まゆしぃは とっても悲しいし
恥ずかしいのです
Jeez!
ったく… 風呂場をのぞいた上に
Not only did you peep on us in the shower,
you forgot all the shopping!
買い出しも
全部 忘れてきたって？
I can't believe it!
ホント 信じらんない！
Hey, Okabe!
ちょっと 岡部？
オカリン？
Okarin?
あっ ダル君
It's Daru-kun!
What's wrong?
どうしたの？ こんな夜に
Why are you here so late?
うん…
I knew it.
やっぱり…
When I accessed it from the outside,
外から パソコン アクセスして
何か変と思ってたんだけど…
I thought there was something weird.
Is something wrong?
何か あったの？
今 ここ
The lab is connected directly to the heart of SERN.
ＳＥＲＮの中心部と ダイレクトで
回線がつながってる
SERN?
ＳＥＲＮ？
システムを掌握したというのか？
You've taken over their system?
I guess so. I win the internet!
まあね キリッ
Or so I'd like to say,
と言いたいところだけど
but to be honest, I was connected
before I even knew it.
実際は 何か分からないうちに
つながっていた
SERN's been standing naked, outside my house,
いつの間にか ＳＥＲＮが 勝手に
全裸待機してた的な
this whole time.
Say what now?
ｗｋｔｋ？
ちょっと待って！
Wait!
If we're connected,
without our having done anything,
こっちが何もしてないのに
つながっているって…
doesn't that imply that they've found us out,
つまり ＳＥＲＮの方が
こっちの動きに気付いて
and are connecting to us?
逆に アクセスしてきたって
ことじゃないの？
あっ…
Hmm... But I don't think I've made any errors
that would have gotten us caught.
う～ん… でも バレるような
ヘマは してないはずだし…
Now we can use the LHC all we want.
今なら こっちから
ＬＨＣだって…
It can't be...
まさか… ＳＥＲＮ？
SERN!
The LHC?
オカリン？
Okarin?
うん？ 携帯に何かあったの？
Is something wrong with your phone?
No...
いや… 何でもない…
Nothing.
ここはね
7,000万年前の地球だよ
まゆり？